that does show pretty thick plumes up here and a light amount of smoke around Colorado.
cue-001777
percent up to 75 percent for precipitation so a little uptick there and you can see two weeks ago
cue-001780
Rockies and of the last seven days much more significant and coverage statewide, which is what we were expecting. So
cue-001782-02
We got skipped for the most part. I got 0.47 inches of rain with that storm a couple nights
cue-001787
a look at severe weather the climatology through the late spring and into the summer you can
cue-001789
there but the last week of July it really decreases things are get a lot
cue-001790
quieter as severe weather goes
cue-001792
excessive moisture it's really precipitation and that's not severe
cue-001793
that's not severe weather unless you have floods but that's a different
cue-001794
warning category so we do have a little chance of mainly wind
cue-001796
Continued chance of convection for Saturday. It's really in the mountains and just maybe a storm or two
cue-001800
front draped along it is cooler out there low 80s so kind of nice on Thursday
cue-001802
We have the potential for heavy flooding rains with thunderstorms and the severe is out here in Kansas.
cue-001804
the coverage precipitation on Friday. And it's Western Colorado for Saturday. Really, I don't
cue-001807-02
25 but we'll see. We are topped out with our maximum temperature day and night 60 and 90.
cue-001809
For August 1st 2008 record low 42. That's the record low for all of
cue-001811
occurred occurred on the 31st and 1873 and the next day 1995 I'll go back
cue-001815
And that brings in cloudiness Monday through Friday. So definitely decreasing sunlight and
cue-001818
expected almost everywhere so that's four six seven eight you know almost an
cue-001819
inch maybe over the week I'd be great some people get a lot more Saturday
cue-001821
So, that's not going to be great.
cue-001821-02
You can see in the water vapor satellite image here, this is Bertha down here, a little tropical